Sahara. Algeria
a smuggling route
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
What do you believe in. Carlos?
I don't understand. I don't speak English.
Yes. you do.
I speak English.
I speak good English.
Misty…
I believe in love.
Love is all we have.
Two people.
Connection.
What are you doing?
Do you know who we are?
Who is our boss?
Shut your mouth!
Wichser.
Please. brother. let me go.
Pray to your god.
Are you English?
Can you talk to them? Tell them I work for the cartel.
- From Guinea-Bissau. This is our route. - Your time has come.
Accept it.
Ask God for help.
- Pray. - I'm a drug courier.
I don't pray!
And it's not over for me.
Come on. man. Where are you from?
Who are you?
No. please don't. I don't want to die.
Don't kill me!
Get her in the truck. Now!
Beilung!
In the back.
The!
- Come in. - I need to get something.
- Get in. damn it. - Please. it's just a photo.
It's in my car.
If you lie. I'll kill you.
Do you see.
Move.
The. the.
Get in the damn car.
- Drive. - Where to?
Just drive.
Caucasus Mountains Russia
a Russian smuggling route
The boxes belong to the contraband.
I wasn't told that.
There are two of them.
Nobody told me that…
what's in the boxes?
My name is Oksana Shirokova.
Do you know the name?
Then you should know that you shouldn't ask questions...
…but do what you're told.
Listen.
Remember. they should always be separate from each other.
Understood?
I won't disappoint you.
You have two days.
Where did you take the goods?
Beirut.
I thought to Libya.
- The drugs are for Europe. right? - Normally. yes... but not today.
We came from Bissau via Mali to Algeria…
…then Libya. then I will be flown to Beirut.
This is no ordinary trip.
Go to Libya. but not to the plane.
- Take me to Benghazi. - I can't.
You will.
I just saved your life.
You owe me something.
Are they gendarmes or military?
- Gendarmes. I think. - Do you know them?
Does the cartel also pay them?
If you save me. part of the goods will be yours.
Don't get out.
Don't say a word.
Are you letting me down?
…I'll shoot you through the seat.
Into the spine.
Stop.
Captain Septi.
Max…
…from Bissau.
What is that?
What is this. Max?
Where is your car?
Uh. we… nous…
uh. meeting…
Islamist fighters?
Yes.
Uh. peng. peng. peng.
Uh. my car… my car is broken.
I had to take this truck.
My partner Carlos…
…to.
That was a fucking cauchemar. mate.
Nightmare.
For you.
Here.
I think you have a problem.
Was?
Max. me?
- Yeah. what's wrong with that? - Nothing.
Max.
Do you think you're Mad Max. Max?
Driving through the desert.
deliver drugs. do crazy stuff. right?
No. I don't.
What's your name?
Fahr.
Only AK ammunition. Caliber 7.62.
One side fired. not the narcos.
And not a jihadist.
Of course. Sherlock. I see he's not here.
Kidnapping. Kill the narcos. steal the equipment. and then the twist.
He kills his own people.
I'm telling you. this jerk is evil.
No loyalty. he's a rat.
Head north… maybe Benghazi.
We almost had him.
I've been after that jerk for years.
Just a matter of time. huh?
Okay. what now?
Tee.
A storm is brewing.
Was that one of the Russian boxes?
No.
The! The! The!
Thank God. The witch would have killed us all.
Keep going.
I don't see the way.
When does your flight to Beirut leave?
Tomorrow evening.
- And if you miss him? - I'll be killed.
This is not good.
Are you a jihadist?
You don't even know what jihad means.
Yes. I know that.
Kill everyone who doesn't believe the same as you.
No.
Jihad means problems.
It can be anything.
Earning money. starting a family. personal struggles that each of us
with the trials that Allah imposes on us.
Was that a test? From God? When you shot your friends?
The way you pass the exams.
decides whether you are righteous or damned.
Why her death?
I am a damned one.
Of…
you are a supplier.
You could work for Amazon.
They don't pay that well.
I am not a supplier.
- I'm a drug courier. - You're a shitty delivery driver.
- Accept that. - I don't just smuggle drugs.
Not?
No.
Also antiques.
That's why I'm going to Beirut.
What kind of antiques?
The statue.
The statue?
Guinea Bissau West Africa
African headquarters of a drug cartel
Small statues. Very valuable.
The payment... is the delivery.
You go to Beirut and get the statues.
You take them to Marrakesh.
Morocco? Why Morocco?
- Why are they asking. Max? - I want to know what I'm doing. Danny.
You do what I tell you.
The statues must be transported separately.
Two statues…
…you and Carlos. two men.
- Why separate? - Because Antonio Alam wants it that way.
He is the boss.
Have fun.
- Talk to Miguel. okay? - Do you want a girl before you go?
No. man. Thanks.
It's all ok.
Didn't sleep?
No.
I don't sleep much.
This is not good.
Clean the windows.
When I saw you outside. I thought you were praying.
I don't pray anymore.
Then why should I pray? When you almost killed me?
People like to pray before they die.
I don't believe in God.
Religion. none of that shit.
What do you think?
I believe in love.
Who you love?
I love my girlfriend.
That's nice. isn't it?
You were lucky there.
I tell her that all the time.
I knew it the moment I saw her.
What is your girl's name?
Laetitia.
Is she in Guinea-Bissau?
No.
No. she is in Spain.
I had to come here to work for the cartel.
Where are you from? From the north?
Damn. you're exhausting.
You are English.
- You can admit that. - Not anymore.
What do you think?
I am stateless. No passport.
You can't go home?
- Never? - Never.
What do you see there?
Nothing.
- Sure? - Get in.
Rein.
Why do you want to go to Benghazi? Benghazi is a place to disappear.
Do you want that?
Just take me there. That's all you need to know.
I know that Benghazi is our target.
But there is an oasis that the Bedouins use.
From there I get a ride to Benghazi.
- If you want. - Take me to Benghazi.
Yes. ready.
No problem.
They must remain separate.
Yes I know.
This is valuable Russian cargo.
Do you know what it is?
To you they are statues.
You are safe with me.
- Will you tell me your name? - No.
- You're not Jihadi John. are you? - He's dead.
Oh. yes. That's true.
Jihadi John…
…is fucking dead.
A bomb hit his fucking skull.
- You talk a lot. don't you? - I need a name for you.
I could call you jihadi John 2.
- I'll call you jj. - You don't.
If you don't tell me. I have to.
- I have no choice. - Slow down.
What are you doing?
We need gasoline.
What do you think happened?
They were killed.
From people like you?
Perhaps.
Maybe they killed the people who smuggled them.
- Do you have anything? - A little. We need more.
Okay. let's go.
I don't know how far we'll get.
It's okay.
We'll clean this up. boy.
We'll get you something to eat.
You don't understand a word. do you?
Whatever you say.
that will hurt like hell.
We need more gasoline.
I said I know an oasis nearby.
We can take him there…
…with the money in your backpack you could come to Europe.
And I'm going to Beirut. I could still make my flight.
Okay.
Go there.
Beirut Lebanon
a turning point
You are ready.
My son…
We belong to Allah. and to Him we shall return.
He was a good son.
What do we do now?
The Brit.
He will pay for this with his life.
Sahara. Libya
an oasis
How you do that?
Is someone behind me?
So?
There are Bedouins here who can take him to Benghazi.
And then? Sell him on the slave market?
He can go from there to Europe.
You can also go.
I'm not going with him.
Then you can only give him a chance.
You are on your own.
I can't do anything more for you.
Trying to survive.
Hey.
No. what are you doing? No. stop.
Go.
Get lost.
Come on.
Let's go.
Worth it.
Did you kill children before?
One shot?
Strapped a suicide bomb to someone?
Yes. that makes sense.
You try to save the child to make amends.
As I said.
God sends trials.
Damn right.
You have to decide.
We can't stay here forever.
Tomorrow I'm going to Benghazi.
You go your way...
...deliver your drugs. go to Beirut.
I'll take the money and make sure he comes to Europe.
If that's what you want.
Thank you. You didn't kill me.
It's okay.
I owe you something for that.
Go.
- Come on. you fucking thing. - Move!
I'll try. man.
The!
Exit!
Did you kill my son?
We have welcomed you.
We treated you like one of us.
My son saw you as a brother.
You betrayed him.
You are a traitor.
You are a devil.
The Bedouins would have been safe.
I should have left him in the truck.
His death was planned this way.
- Nothing is planned. - Yes. everything.
I'll know when my death is near. And so will you.
The delivery is gone.
They burned them.
It should be a means of payment…
…for the statues my boss bought in Beirut.
Then don't go to Beirut.
Without cargo. the cartel will hunt you down.
I work for them. I have no choice.
They might think you're dead.
Your chance to dive in.
They always find you.
During the exchange of fire you ran
and hid at the truck.
You're a coward. Max. huh?
Are you afraid of violence?
As a drug dealer. you are afraid of violence.
I'm just a driver. I don't kill people.
I don't have to.
And I won't.
I am not like you.
You kill everyone.
I didn't kill you.
And why not?
No. come on. tell me. You could have killed me.
You could have taken everything - the coke. the money.
You changed your mind. You looked up at the sky.
and changed your mind. What was it? A sign?
- A sign? - Yes. a sign.
From Allah… whatever.
What was it?
It was a drone.
A drone?
Like this one?
Run.
Oh. now I've got you. you jerk.
A damn drone?
- I thought you saw an angel. - I don't see any angels. just drones.
- What are you doing? - I'll get you.
- What? What's going on? - The sun.
Shit.
Come on!
I thought you didn't pray anymore.
Damn it!
Don't stop. I can see them!
What was it?
A bird.
An eagle.
- Drive! - Okay!
Let's see how well you wankers know the desert.
Shit. drive!
- Who's chasing you? - Someone with a drone.
- Who has drones? - Lots of people. they're cheap.
Armies have drones.
Damn it.
- Did we lose them? - I don't see anything.
Perhaps the bird was a sign. The eagle.
- A sign from God. - For what?
That you should come with me to Beirut to get the statues.
- I'm not going to Beirut. - What else do you want to do?
I don't know it.
It's a two-man job. Me and Carlos. The one who was killed.
Maybe you owe me something and should help me.
I don't owe you anything.
A simple job. very quick.
In and out. You and me.
The bird was not a sign from God to go to Beirut.
No. but he answered your prayers.
How do you get there?
Between…
…my friend.
Do we fly with it?
- Through the night? - Yes. you can sleep.
We arrive early.
We were attacked. The shipment is gone. that's true.
But I say. you saved me. The cartel is sending other cargo.
We still have to get the statues and get out of here.
- Do you think they believe that? - Yes.
Why not?
No one from the cartel will be there and I am very credible.
Credible?
Is that you?
Hello.
Good morning.
It's bottom left.
THANKS.
In and out. remember?
- And let me do the talking. - Yes. yes.
Danny.
What are you doing here?
You had trouble?
Yes.
We met jihadists.
They stole the shipment.
Carlos died in the process.
Why did I have to hear that from the gendarmes?
Why not from you?
I lost my phone.
How should I speak to you?
I wanted to stick to the plan.
Get the statues of Alam.
That was important to me.
It's important. How are you going to pay for the statues without delivery?
And who the hell is that?
This is yy.
He saved my life.
Saved your life?
That's not my name.
I saved his life.
Danny. come on. man.
You can't kill him.
Get out of the way.
Drop it. Danny.
- Max. what the hell are you doing? - I'm serious.
What will you do. Max?
Are you going to kill me?
You fucking coward.
Are you going to shoot me?
Holy shit!
You bastard!
Thanks.
Where are the statues?
There must be two.
We'll take them with us.
Don't look at him. do it.
You tried to kill us. so we're taking your statues.
If you want them back. you have to pay us.
You're going to die. coño.
We all will.
Get the other one.
Hurry up!
No movement!
Don't take it. Please.
Worth it.
- Keep them two meters apart. - Max. go.
Max.
We're not finished yet.
You can't shoot.
The bags could explode.
Shit!
They contain uranium.
Nuclear fuel.
The whole city explodes.
Next time…
A quick job? In. out.
Dr. cassandra Bryce?
I'm from the drug squad here in Beirut.
I have information for which I need your nuclear knowledge.
What the hell is this?
My name is Antonio Alam.
The boss of the cartel.
Listen carefully. Max.
The metal in the boxes is uranium.
My source said it's 50 kilos of uranium.
For a bomb.
- A dirty bomb? - A Hiroshima bomb.
Subtitles By: Jessica young
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today